[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '幼稚園' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ようちえん"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '植物園' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょくぶつえん"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '遊園地' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ゆうえんち"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お寺' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おてら"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '八百屋' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "やおや"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '体育館' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たいいくかん"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '大使館' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たいしかん"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '消防署' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょうぼうしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '警察署' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けいさつしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '博物館' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はくぶつかん"
    }
]
